(Amy:)...can map memory sequences
in dendritic branches...
(Amy:)...made the cover of Neuron.
Ooh! Peaking of good news,
somebody just hit 100 Twitter followers.
That's nice. Anyway, l've been
dreaming of this day for a long time.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, me too. Triple digits.
I'm not gonna lie, feels pretty good.
(Amy:)I'm the sole author on a paper
being published...
(Amy:)...in a distinguished journal that
may change the course of my field.
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Ooh!
One-oh-one!
Air's getting a bit thin up here.
(Penny:)So are we ready to order?
(Amy:)Give me a minute.
I'm gonna go wash up.
(Sheldon:)Well, that's odd.
We both washed up when we came in.
(Sheldon:)It's probably a euphemism
for urination.
- Sheldon, what is wrong with you?
- Not much.
AIthough I can be fauIted
for being overly fond of koala bears.
I don't know what it is, when they start
munching on eucalyptus, I meIt inside.